[
    {
        "question": "Which international airport sits on an artificial island?",
        "answer": "Hong Kong International Airport"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Florida city is known as the `Winter Strawberry Capital of the World`?",
        "answer": "Plant City"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Gulf of Oman connects the Persian Gulf with what sea?",
        "answer": "Arabian Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the seismic fault line located at the conjunction of Missouri, Arkansas, and Tennessee?",
        "answer": "New Madrid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Canadian Province is located between Saskatchewan and Ontario?",
        "answer": "Manitoba"
    },
    {
        "question": "The historic district of Haight-Ashbury is located in what US city?",
        "answer": "San Francisco"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year did Atlanta become the fifth capital of Georgia?",
        "answer": "1868"
    },
    {
        "question": "A statue of Billy Bremner stands outside the ground of which football stadium?",
        "answer": "Leeds United"
    },
    {
        "question": "What word is used to identify the residents of Burkina Faso?",
        "answer": "Burkinabe"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Belize known as until 1973?",
        "answer": "British Honduras"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which popular artist was born as Robyn Fenty in 1988 in Barbados?",
        "answer": "Rihanna"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Republic of Benin shares a border with which other African country to the east?",
        "answer": "Nigeria"
    },
    {
        "question": "Until 1989, what European country was the world`s second largest exporter of bottled wine?",
        "answer": "Bulgaria"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which Brazilian city was F1 driver Ayrton Senna born?",
        "answer": "S\u00e3o Paulo"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the longest mountain range on land?",
        "answer": "The Andes"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US city would you find the Space Needle?",
        "answer": "Seattle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two South American countries do not share a land boundary with Brazil?",
        "answer": "Chile and Ecuador"
    },
    {
        "question": "What harbor is overlooked by Victoria Peak?",
        "answer": "Hong Kong"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where would you find Olympus Mons?",
        "answer": "Mars"
    },
    {
        "question": "What range contains the world`s highest mountains not located in Asia?",
        "answer": "The Andes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders both of the world`s only two nations with square flags?",
        "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state`s civil law is most closely based on the Napoleonic Code?",
        "answer": "Louisiana`s"
    },
    {
        "question": "Of the US states that border Mexico, which shares the shortest border?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is known as the `Biggest Little City in the World`?",
        "answer": "Reno"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river do the Holland Tunnel and Lincoln Tunnel pass beneath?",
        "answer": "Hudson River"
    },
    {
        "question": "Washington D.C. is located on the shores of what river?",
        "answer": "Potomac River"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only country that begins with the letter `O` ?",
        "answer": "Oman"
    },
    {
        "question": "What capital city is located on the shores of Chesapeake Bay?",
        "answer": "Annapolis"
    },
    {
        "question": "The city of Albuquerque is located in what desert?",
        "answer": "Chihuahua Desert"
    },
    {
        "question": "What nation removed the prefix `Trans` from before its name in June 1949?",
        "answer": "Jordan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is the eastern terminus of the Trans-Siberian Railway?",
        "answer": "Vladivostok"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Canadian territory came into existence on April 1, 1999?",
        "answer": "Nunavut"
    },
    {
        "question": "What European country ruled Macau until December 20, 1999?",
        "answer": "Portugal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Prior to August 1984, Burkina Faso was known by what name?",
        "answer": "The Republic of Upper Volta"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Republic of Upper Volta was the official name of which African country before August 1984?",
        "answer": "Burkina Faso"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US coast is the state of Maryland located on?",
        "answer": "East"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the nickname for Alaska?",
        "answer": "The Last Frontier"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state has a Thames River?",
        "answer": "Connecticut"
    },
    {
        "question": "What airport has the code MME?",
        "answer": "Durham Tees Valley"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest city by area in the continental United States?",
        "answer": "Sitka, Alaska"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is located at the junction of the Allegheny River and Monongahela River?",
        "answer": "Pittsburgh"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is located on the shores of Rapid Creek?",
        "answer": "Rapid City"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Guggenheim Museum is located in what city?",
        "answer": "New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Missouri River flows into what river?",
        "answer": "Mississippi River"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is located on the shores of Puget Sound?",
        "answer": "Seattle"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest lake found completely within the United States?",
        "answer": "Lake Michigan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the shallowest sea on Earth?",
        "answer": "Sea of Azov"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the second smallest country in the world?",
        "answer": "Monaco"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city is the only one located on two continents?",
        "answer": "Istanbul"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is home to the Finger Lakes?",
        "answer": "New York"
    }
]